[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Are you a bit mystified that people aren't really galvanized yet into Mitt Romney being the nominee?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "bit", "mystified", "that", "people", "are", "n't", "really", "galvanized", "yet", "into", "Mitt", "Romney", "being", "the", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Look, we're focused on getting the delegates we need to get the nomination.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "we", "'re", "focused", "on", "getting", "the", "delegates", "we", "need", "to", "get", "the", "nomination", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Is that really helpful to either Mitt Romney or to the party itself?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "really", "helpful", "to", "either", "Mitt", "Romney", "or", "to", "the", "party", "itself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, we always knew that this would be a long fight.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "always", "knew", "that", "this", "would", "be", "a", "long", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "I mean how far do you take on Rick Santorum in that kind of territory?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "how", "far", "do", "you", "take", "on", "Rick", "Santorum", "in", "that", "kind", "of", "territory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, at first we challenge the statement that he's not a true conservative.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "first", "we", "challenge", "the", "statement", "that", "he", "'s", "not", "a", "true", "conservative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What do you think have been the main things that he's learned so far on this campaign trail?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "have", "been", "the", "main", "things", "that", "he", "'s", "learned", "so", "far", "on", "this", "campaign", "trail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "You know, I think just getting his message out is the most important thing.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "just", "getting", "his", "message", "out", "is", "the", "most", "important", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "I mean, do you think it's time that one of the contestants, maybe more than one, consider whether to pull out?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "time", "that", "one", "of", "the", "contestants", ",", "maybe", "more", "than", "one", ",", "consider", "whether", "to", "pull", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "CD", ",", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "You know, that's going to be up to all the individual campaigns, and I'll let their campaigns decide that.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "up", "to", "all", "the", "individual", "campaigns", ",", "and", "I", "'ll", "let", "their", "campaigns", "decide", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "How are you actually going to win this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "actually", "going", "to", "win", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, first of all, there's a couple of things that the Romney people, for some reason, always seem to fail to tell anybody and that is that many of the delegates that are already there are not binding delegates.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "couple", "of", "things", "that", "the", "Romney", "people", ",", "for", "some", "reason", ",", "always", "seem", "to", "fail", "to", "tell", "anybody", "and", "that", "is", "that", "many", "of", "the", "delegates", "that", "are", "already", "there", "are", "not", "binding", "delegates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Newt Gingrich"]}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Could you see Newt Gingrich doing that?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "see", "Newt", "Gingrich", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "Well, look, Newt Gingrich is going to have to do what Newt Gingrich has to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "look", ",", "Newt", "Gingrich", "is", "going", "to", "have", "to", "do", "what", "Newt", "Gingrich", "has", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "DT", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 147, "question": "And finally, John, and briefly if you don't mind, can we assume that we will not be seeing Rick Santorum uttering the word snob again in this campaign, or actually college education, and that he will desist from saying John F. Kennedy made him throw up?", "question_tokens": ["And", "finally", ",", "John", ",", "and", "briefly", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", ",", "can", "we", "assume", "that", "we", "will", "not", "be", "seeing", "Rick", "Santorum", "uttering", "the", "word", "snob", "again", "in", "this", "campaign", ",", "or", "actually", "college", "education", ",", "and", "that", "he", "will", "desist", "from", "saying", "John", "F.", "Kennedy", "made", "him", "throw", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 148, "answer": "Well, you know, the interesting thing, I will say this, this probably the first campaign in the history of political -- of presidential politics in recent history that we do not have a pollsters, we do not have wordsmiths always telling the candidate what to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "interesting", "thing", ",", "I", "will", "say", "this", ",", "this", "probably", "the", "first", "campaign", "in", "the", "history", "of", "political", "--", "of", "presidential", "politics", "in", "recent", "history", "that", "we", "do", "not", "have", "a", "pollsters", ",", "we", "do", "not", "have", "wordsmiths", "always", "telling", "the", "candidate", "what", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John", "Rick Santorum", "John F. Kennedy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 229, "question": "What was your memory of the whole process?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "memory", "of", "the", "whole", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well, first of all, let me say, I am not going to see \"Game Change.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "let", "me", "say", ",", "I", "am", "not", "going", "to", "see", "``", "Game", "Change", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "What goes through the mind of a wife in this situation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "goes", "through", "the", "mind", "of", "a", "wife", "in", "this", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "It is day by day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "day", "by", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Well, the prize is so great, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "prize", "is", "so", "great", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "It is great.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "But do you think it is time that one or two of the candidates pulled out?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "think", "it", "is", "time", "that", "one", "or", "two", "of", "the", "candidates", "pulled", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "Well, let's step back just a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "step", "back", "just", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 346, "question": "I mean did you think that he was being bigoted, Kirk Cameron?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "did", "you", "think", "that", "he", "was", "being", "bigoted", ",", "Kirk", "Cameron", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "You know --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kirk Cameron"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Is it too harsh to say that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "too", "harsh", "to", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "CCAIN: It is too harsh.", "answer_tokens": ["CCAIN", ":", "It", "is", "too", "harsh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "And what did you think of Rush Limbaugh's comments?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "think", "of", "Rush", "Limbaugh", "'s", "comments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I -- I am -- I'm strongly -- I strongly disagree.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "am", "--", "I", "'m", "strongly", "--", "I", "strongly", "disagree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "But that's the sense that came through, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "that", "'s", "the", "sense", "that", "came", "through", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Yes, I know.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Should someone like him be on air after saying something so offensive?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "someone", "like", "him", "be", "on", "air", "after", "saying", "something", "so", "offensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "What do you think of this video clip?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "this", "video", "clip", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, it's a very interesting video clip.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "interesting", "video", "clip", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Who cares?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "cares", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Law school.", "answer_tokens": ["Law", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Why didn't we see it in 2007 or 2008?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "n't", "we", "see", "it", "in", "2007", "or", "2008", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "It's an indictment of Ben.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "indictment", "of", "Ben", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2007", "2008"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "What's your view of all this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "view", "of", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "I have to correct Ben real quick, because we actually had the footage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "to", "correct", "Ben", "real", "quick", ",", "because", "we", "actually", "had", "the", "footage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Is it a valid thing to whack the president with or is it a lot of hot air about nothing, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "valid", "thing", "to", "whack", "the", "president", "with", "or", "is", "it", "a", "lot", "of", "hot", "air", "about", "nothing", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "I am just worried about it becoming a distraction.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "just", "worried", "about", "it", "becoming", "a", "distraction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "It would seem, from an outsider, that Romney is going to walk this, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "seem", ",", "from", "an", "outsider", ",", "that", "Romney", "is", "going", "to", "walk", "this", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "I think it's not a question of if.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "question", "of", "if", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "They've got to work out the moment when they are going to press the button on the nominee, haven't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'ve", "got", "to", "work", "out", "the", "moment", "when", "they", "are", "going", "to", "press", "the", "button", "on", "the", "nominee", ",", "have", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I don't know if there's the moment, but they certainly don't want it to go all the way up to the convention.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "there", "'s", "the", "moment", ",", "but", "they", "certainly", "do", "n't", "want", "it", "to", "go", "all", "the", "way", "up", "to", "the", "convention", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Or does the constant mudslinging by his competitors now in his party kill the brand a bit?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "does", "the", "constant", "mudslinging", "by", "his", "competitors", "now", "in", "his", "party", "kill", "the", "brand", "a", "bit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "He seems to be -- I agree with Amy.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "seems", "to", "be", "--", "I", "agree", "with", "Amy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["July"]}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Let me start with you, Carol?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "start", "with", "you", ",", "Carol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "July.", "answer_tokens": ["July", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Amy?", "question_tokens": ["Amy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "The month when it is exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "month", "when", "it", "is", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Dana?", "question_tokens": ["Dana", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "July probably.", "answer_tokens": ["July", "probably", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["May", "June"]}, "docId": "120307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 671, "question": "Ben?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 672, "answer": "I think they'll lock it up in May, maybe confirm it in June.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "'ll", "lock", "it", "up", "in", "May", ",", "maybe", "confirm", "it", "in", "June", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]